Through the eternal time, the human world
And heaven both live in peace,
everything happens according to destiny.
It is said that
the Heaven of Emperor
has pre-written everything's fate
in the Sealed Book,
like a script waiting to be played out.
But some believe,
people should decide on their own fate.
Just like how Zixia believes that
Joker is the one she is destined to love.
However, in Joker's heart,
there is only place for his wife,
Pak Jing Jing.
Zixia refuses to accept such fate,
decides to use the moonlight box to travel
through time in order to preview the future.
After learning how everything would end,
She is determined to change
the outcome against all odds.
Zixia...
Take it
Zixia
Zixia, Zixia.
What did you see in the future?
Why are you breaking up with me now?
Why? Why... Wh
Stop, don't come closer!
Ok, I stay!
Then tell me,
when you time traveled with the
Moonlight box? What did you see?
I saw another woman in
your heart-Pak Jing Jing.
She said such things to you.
Your conscience told me,
it is not me who you love,
but another woman,
when I saw the mark she
had left in your heart,
I realized that it is not me who you have
been searching in the past 500 years,
but her.
You and I should both believe, it is fate,
what they also call destiny.
What she has left, was a drop of tear.
When her tear drop melt with your heart,
You will forget me, and
falls in love with her.
He cannot fall in love with me!
Zixia
Why don't you tell him how it would end?
If he finds out that he is the Monkey King,
it will terrify him.
Didn't you always want
to marry a great hero?
But I saw how it would end,
he cannot fall in love with me,
if he falls in love with me, I would die.
No, I have to bring him
back to Pak Jing Jing.
Coming!
Zixia!
Am I seeing this for real? Zixia...
Ah That Pak woman you want me to meet,
whatever her name is.
Pak Jing Jing
Why?
She is to be your wife 500 years later.
Aren't you my wife?
Shut up! And wait for me here.
Only a true wife can order
her husband around,
I feel we are becoming
more like a couple, Yes!
Don't go in. Pak Jing Jing is
fighting the Snake Demon
over a man!
How dare you ask me to leave him?
Yes, how dare you? Yes! How Dare you?
How dare you?
So what! I don't like you! So what.
Because of these 100 pieces of silver.
Whatever can be bought cannot be sincere!
So what you are rich,
it's not even that much money.
Stop, all of you.
Pretty boy does not have a conscience.
If love can be bought with
100 pieces of silver,
then I offer 500 pieces.
So generous.
Whatever I offer to her, I can give to you
This trick can only fool little girls
Because I love you two so much,
I would give my life to prove it.
Wow! Are you serious?
How could such wonderful man exists?
They fight just like
how you fought with Lady Spring.
How long haven't you seen her?
Last I heard,
you dumped her after you
met the Monkey King.
Snake, it's none of your business.
You think I want to care?
He is looking all over for you.
So what if he finds me?
I'm not afraid of him.
Forget it, do your thing
Saire, Saire!
Such a pretty face and nice body
No wonder Joker is all over you.
Who is Joker? Who are you?
Who am I!
I am the matchmaker sent by god.
I am engaged to that stupid Monkey.
I have no feeling for other men.
I hate you girls,
Spend all day chasing
after that stupid money
That was my sister, hope
she didn't scare you.
Listen, Joker is the Monkey King
from 500 years later.
He is now a pretty boy,
dump the Monkey, marry him instead.
Oh, you must be one of Monkey's women,
Trying to make me dump Monkey
for that Jo whatever?
Joker
Don't even think about
making me leaving Monkey,
That Joker dude, you can
keep him for yourself.
I am not easily fooled.
Keep trying then I will kill you.
Silly tricks, you are going to die
Hey, what do you want?
What? I'm trying to kill her
Sister, no!
No more bullshit
Calm down, sister!
Which sister?
You decided yet? My sister is taking over.
Get out of my way!
Calm down, please!
Let me take over!
Spare me the split personality act,
I'd rather die than marrying the Joker.
What happened?
I don't know. Fell down
in a blink of an eye.
I ask you again,
are you marrying him or not? Huh?
She is forcing me to marry!
Forcing you? Who dares
to commit such evil act!
What happened?
I don't know. Fell down
in a blink of an eye.
Was I too fast? Should I do it again?
- I will kill you!
- I won't let you get away with this!
Hahaha...
Ah!
Do you yield?
Yes..yes
If someone gives you trouble later,
say my name!
Yes, boss!
What boss? I'm no
gangbanger, call me master.
Yes, Master!
Good, call me master, bow to my will.
Yes
First job for you.
What is it?
To seduce a man.
What? To seduce a man?
Him, come in!
Yes! Coming, coming
What I want is true love,
if the price for such love is
to leave Joker all alone in life,
I'd rather be the one who is lonely.
I use to believe in fate,
but now I believe in myself only.
I must rewrite this tragedy.
Creating a happy ending for Joker
and his wife Pak Jing Jing.
You are...
Don't know you. Ok, let's go.
You don't know her?
She is your wife Pak Jing Jing!
He's joker, your husband
from 500 years later.
500 later?
Yes!
I don't get it!
Enough talking, let's go.
- What?
- Well, this is what happened.
Let me fill you in.
In a very dark night,
you, Pak Jing Jing, him, Joker,
sparked up a romantic love affair.
He turned around, you pointed at him,
his hands caught fire,
and you caught him.
You hit him harder and harder, and harder.
And then,
the story reached its
turning point and climax,
you may fill in the blanks yourself,
now to the point,
In order to save you, he used the
moonlight box to travel through time,
but the box failed to work,
Bang! Here we are, this is what happened.
So sorry about this.
My wife has a bit of a mental issue,
let's go home for the medicine, lets go...
I am not ill, let me go.
You have to be ill
I am not ill.
Hey, what you doing?
Look at this, this is the jade plate that
you will give to him 500 years later,
he brings with him at all times.
That is hers.
I don't mind you to have Monkey King,
Of course I wouldn't mind you
to have a second man,
but you cannot leave me out of the loop.
Who are they to you?
Isn't it obvious? Of course they have
something to do with me.
Shut up!
Don't even think about getting
close to Pak Jing Jing.
Then why won't you leave Jing Jing alone?
She has her Joker, you
have your second chief.
What second chief.
Your baby daddy.
What...
See? She says what?...are you ill?
See I told you she is sick,
you wouldn't believe me.
Ok, let's go home for medicine, lets go.
Ask him if you will, did she have a baby
with the second chief, I am not ill.
Wait, before I know you,
I did have a lot of boyfriends,
but I do not know any second chief,
which means it was a one night stand,
I don't even remember
the baby daddy's name,
How could I remember that I had a son?
OK, then!
So you go on your merry way,
we split from now on.
Hey, I am the one who dumps people,
Stop, you bitch!
Time for medicine
Let me go, what are you doing.
Its their business, you should let
them handle it
Pak Jing Jing is your wife.
You already messed them up enough,
Now you want me to help making it worse.
God has made you and I a couple,
can't we focus on us first?
You cannot like me
Why not?
Because, because you met her first.
No, I met you first.
How come?
You traveled 500 years to meet me,
in order to find her.
You are from 500 years ago,
I met her 500 years later,
of course I met you first.
But
I just sort out 500 years of mess.
Let's move on, give me a kiss...
What you doing?
You stink!
I get it,
You are now Qingxia,
That's why you hit me,
but love is fearless, I won't let
your sister intimidate me.
I get it! Love needs time,
Calm yourself.
Wow, sword...
Why did you hit him?
He tried to kiss me, of
course I would hit him.
You want to die, to end with a tragedy,
I will not be part of it.
No,
I cannot let that tragedy happen again,
to leave him alone like this.
Oh damn, you are doomed.
What? I just don't want to die,
So I must fix it.
You are trying to rewrite the end,
of course everything is messed up.
Ok
That's it. History says
I cannot marry the King Bull,
Now I can do it.
If I marry the King Bull,
Joker will give up, then I won't die.
Ok, I need to go to the King Bull.
Zixia, where are you?
Zixia? Where are you?
Ahh, Zixia!
Zixia, where are you?
If I don't get out of
this desert, I will die
Zixia,
What the hell?
Monkey King,
You promised Buddha to accompany
the Longevity monk to go on the pilgrimage.
Monkey King?
But now you dare to conspire
with the King Bull,
intending to eat your master
Spare me the talk,
you chased me for 3 days,
I did not hit you because you are a woman,
Don't think that I'm afraid you.
Monkey, how could you talk to
Guanyin like this.
Evil East?
Wrong, it's me, Longevity Monk,
I happened to travel here
using the moonlight box,
you want to kill me, I don't blame you,
but you should not insult Guanyin.
It's me, the master should be
blamed for my pupil's fault,
It affects my brand name.
Listen to him, there he goes with
his non-sense again.
I'm going to kill you,
Because you have taken my moonlight box,
Asshole.
Why won't you see reason?
I stole your moonlight box,
because you wanted to kill me,
or else why would I ran away
using your moonlight box?
You want to kill me, of course I'm running,
if you don't want to kill me,
then I Won't need to run,
you want to... don't you get my reasons?
Don't you get my reasons?
I cannot stand you anymore
You cannot stand me? I cannot stand you.
Ahhh...
Monkey King
I am done with you,
now I shall continue with time travel.
(Casting Spell)
You filthy animal
Insignificant trick,
I piss better than your magic.
Much better, that's it!
But don't you forget,
My golden cudgel is
borrowed from the Dragon King...
It is the Ocean Quieting Needle!
Turn...
Cloud Somersault
I shall enforce justice
on behalf of heaven.
C'mon, what else you got
Capture!
May the Buddha preserve us.
Lord have mercy
Brother!
Brother, where are you?
- Shh
- Ghost
Brother
Who?
Haha... here you are, brother.
Me? Brother?
It is me, King Bull.
King Bull?
Damn, King Bull
You caught the Longevity Monk,
haha, good for you!
Obviously I'm avatar,
how could I be the Longevity Monk, Sir.
Oh Sir, I'd recognize you even
if your turn into ashes.
A monk should not lie,
may the Buddha preserve us.
It is not too late for
you to know that, brother,
let me introduce my new
wife to you, follow me.
Ah
Back!
Jade Emperor, I have captured
the Monkey King by your order.
Thank you for your effort, Guanyin.
When I enter the human world,
I found the world is filled with grievance,
monsters run wild. I do not remember
the Sealed Book record it this way.
Please do not worry, Guanyin.
The Sealed book follows the rule of
the universe, it cannot be wrong.
I hope it is as you have recorded,
Zixia's death can reform the Monkey King,
keeps him motivated to accompany
the Longevity Monk on the pilgrimage.
I shall return to report
the progress to Buddha,
so we can prepare to receive the pilgrims.
Farewell, Master Guanyin.
Six Ears Monkey, your disguise as
the Monkey King
during the pilgrimage has fooled them all,
my plan is finally...
going to succeed!
Come out!
I knew this is a perfect plan.
When I found out the
Sealed Book had an error,
making the Joker born 500 years later than
the Longevity Monk and Piggy,
causing the journey of pilgrimage
to lack one key member.
Fortunately I have decided to have you
to disguise as the Monkey King
until the real one can
take over 500 years later.
This way, no one would know the difference,
haha, such great plan. Hahaha...
You would still need a great actor
like me to play along,
even the Longevity Monk and Guanyin
did not realize that I was a fake,
such genius.
You are right, Six Ears Monkey,
You are a great faker, let's drink to it!
Cheers,
Great working with you.
Speaking of faking,
You are the best, Jade Emperor.
Thank you. But we still need to
do one more thing.
What it is?
To burn you alive...
haha
Haha, you got me with that one.
I really do mean to burn you alive,
you violated the holy law anyways.
If I did not rescue you
from burning in the Great Oven,
why would you be Willing to work for me
Oh, you are looking for this knife?
Take it, I can pass it to you
But you cannot move, you are poisoned,
I'm not. I took the cure.
You ungrateful bastard
I only wish to finish what I started.
Did you remember when Zixia and Qingxia
first entered the heaven,
you seduced Qingxia and violated
the most sacred holy law,
you were meant to be
burnt in the Great Oven.
So even if I execute you now,
you had your fun in the human world,
how could I be called ungrateful?
Ah hahaha...
We agreed on sharing one mortal body,
how come now I only gets control during
the day and you get it for the night?
You would marry to a filth like King Bull
in order to get rid of Joker.
If I do not control our body at night,
that big bull is going to climb on top,
you may be ok with it but I'm not.
Is that the true reason?
Yes
Where is the moonlight box?
Where did you put it?
Who?
Are you afraid? Charlie Chin.
Not afraid, just don't wish to see you here
I know Guanyin is hunting you,
I am here to save you.
Don't you believe me?
Using this, Guanyin can no longer find you,
but I have one condition.
I knew it, how could you be so kind,
Say it.
Why...
did you leave without
saying goodbye that day.
I am a free man,
I do not like to be tied down!
I can forgive your betrayal,
but you cannot betray the Longevity Monk.
Why not?
Monkey King, I have chased
you for three days,
Show yourself.
I can pretend to be Zixia and misguide her,
saying that you have
stolen the moonlight box.
Why would you help me?
Because...
I have seen you making the mistake once,
I will not let it happen again!
Ah, You went to see the player dude.
Who are you?
Who am I?
My Son, someone is asking
who you mother is.
My mother? My mother is
the Iron Fan Princess,
also known as the wife of King Bull,
people call her the first wife.
She specializes in handling
mistresses like you.
Huh?
- Brother Bull, hear me out,
- Brother,
I was just debating
what's for the main course
here you are with the Longevity Monk,
how about we make a Longevity Monk stew?
We are not familiar with each other, right?
Tell him I'm being truthful,
We just met, right?
Get out of here!
Ah!
Ah! Zixia
Ah! Joker
Ah? She is your wife?
You stupid bull
Ah! Wife
Ah, Monkey King...
Ah? Me?
Four people, I thought there were six?
Their relationship seems really
complicated, don't you get it?
How dare you to cheat
on me with a mistress!
Take this token, go find my sister
Bull Xiang Xiang.
- Yes yes,
- Hurry!
- Zixia, get up
- Monkey King... Stop!
Can we talk about this, okay?
There is nothing to talk about!
Come down here, now!
Oh you, never, over my dead body
Coming down or not?
- No way
- It is not up to you
Why are you following me?
I'm not following you, it is fate,
You said we are destined to be together.
I cannot leave, you should get back
to your wife
Lady, what use is it?
He can leave, but his heart stays.
- This is...
- He is... from Mars
What?
He time travels often, hurt his head.
He told me that he went to Mars
Am I wrong?
He only sees you in his eyes.
No, we cannot be together
Why? you said so yourself,
Whoever pulls out the Zi Qing sword,
will be the one you love.
It ends here, we should break up
No!
We have just begun,
how can we break up so soon...
I do not like speedy break up.
I don't like it either
Hey, where do you come from, kiddo?
Let's go!
What, where?
No more break up?
Women are so fickle!
Go! Hurry up!
Stand your ground
What is it?
Spectacular
Damn, Primordial fire
- Hold it
- Ah... What do you mean
Wow! Obviously split personality!
Run!
Hurry, you control the bull head
Ok, I help you, go
Ok
Here you go
Ah...
Its smoking, hurry
Hey! Hey! I can't handle this one...
Shut up and go
Ok ok, I get it. I will attack.
Head on!
Cliff
Grab the horn
Left turn!
You let me do this.
I serve you
I can't hold on any longer!
Hold on!
Hold on, sister
Em!
Hope the ear won't break, we depend on it
Sister
I'm fine
Don't act tough, come back to me and rest
I thought I can only rely on
the fire roller-skates to fly,
how come you fairies can't fly either?
Do you wish me to give you
my fire roller-skates?
Ah? Fire roller-skates?
How come you have them? Ah
Sorry
Heartless.
Shut up
What a mess
Look
Be cool like a man
My brother sent you?
Yes
Hasn't he always looked down on me?
Calls my magic too cruel,
too much relying on form
Wow...
- Shh
- Em...
My brother said, other people had honed
their magic for more than a 1000 years,
I can swallow it with one swift move,
it has no honor.
Sorry..it's just too scary
My brother is a proud man,
I assume he sent you to beg me
because of that woman?
Are you kidding, this is no ordinary woman,
I... can be your sister in law soon,
You cannot eat her!
I respect you because you have
sworn brotherhood with my brother.
Monkey King, you have a silver tongue,
but I am no foolish woman,
Don't fool me
How could my brother marry a god?
Because your brother wants to immigrate,
marrying her will grant him
a green card in heaven!
Longevity Monk, you are only food to me,
You don't get to speak here.
Thank you so much...
You have finally made me realize that
I am a piece of food on this planet,
not from mars!
Are you messing with me
Don't be mad,
if you are upset, we can leave on our own
Nobody leaves until I say so
Bring it on
Oh? A different person?
Yes, I am her sister Qingxia
Split personality, is a
gynecological disease!
Are you alright?
It's the fog
I happened to ate a double heads
snake for breakfast,
Let's see if I can digest
your split personality too.
I'm not afraid
I'll be waiting
You scared me,
I thought you died
Come... I hold you
For you, I will never die
Yes, we shall only die in happiness!
But we cannot be together
Why?
You must be with someone else,
you cannot fall in love with me!
No, no, no, you have to be more clear
Typical relationship struggle,
love without admission,
simply called ineffable difficulties.
One more word
I will stab you not only with pipa,
but with a knife!
Tell me what ineffable difficulty
could you possibly have?
Say it
I used the moonlight box
go to future
to see our ending
ah..
I will die
you become alone
like a dog
so poor
Everybody dies,
if all lovers over think like you do,
the world will filled with despair
No more matchmaking.
But the more we go on right now,
the more sad memories you will have later
I'm not worried, I know King Bull
has the moonlight box,
we can steal it together, then we run off.
Even if we cannot escape fate,
we would have lived to the fullest.
Life happens only once,
you shouldn't miss it!
You are too lovely.
This is the token that proves my adulthood,
you had it made for me,
I have carried it with me at all times.
I came today, not because I have
something to ask of you,
I am here to admit my mistake!
Are you crazy? Coming here to apologize?
Yes, I am crazy!
I am terminally ill with
my obsession to my first love.
I never thought my first true love
will occur after marriage.
Since I met Zixia, I have learned
what is true love,
I have learned how lonely you must
have been for the last 100 years.
What's the use of it now,
Mantis will not come back to life.
Mantis's nature is to
eat his love companion,
He would have eaten you
if I did not kill him!
So what!
He was my true love,
I'd rather be eaten by him,
than being here all alone,
like a living dead!
There is no such thing
as one true love of your life
He is only singing, not talking,
leave him be.
There is such thing as one true love,
and it is sang into a song.
"The past cannot be undone..."
"Red Leaves fall into the dirt"
"The beginning and the end are fated"
"You fly with the clouds..."
"Ocean of despair..."
"Turns the tide of love and hate"
"No one escapes fate in this world..."
"To love, but not to be together..."
"Or I should believe in karma!"
Dare to seduce your big brother's wife?
I will hit...
Two men kissing?
Xiang Xiang...
brother
Brother, hear me out...
Brother, let me explain,
Last time Xiang Xiang drooled over someone,
was 100 years ago
when she fell in love with Mantis.
Looking at her now,
I think she is in love with you!
But it was those two who kissed,
Couldn't she be in love
with the Longevity Monk?
No, Longevity Monk is
only food to Xiang Xiang.
- May the Buddha preserve us!
- May the Buddha preserve us
Ok then I'm out
Please
you...
Xiang Xiang is 180 years
old, and still single,
since she likes you so much,
then as her big brother,
I shall approve this union,
Haha, so it is decided.
Did not know you have a soft side
Of course!
Zixia, honestly speaking
I am no expert for love
Just tell me, how to make you happy?
You are hilarious.
I kissed the Longevity Monk
you don't kill me, but
falls in love with me,
even though I have been a player for years,
but I have never met a woman
who can accept me being bisexual.
It was your kiss with the Longevity Monk
reminded me of my first love.
Xiang Xiang, why wouldn't you listen to me
I said it.
Girls should not go to school.
Who says the girls cannot go to school?
Stop, you! Come back here
Wait...
Come!
Men at their birth are good in nature
Men are born about the same
but habits make them differ.
The classmates did not
know that I was a girl,
They felt that I was different.
And I did not care how people see how I met
and fell in love with Mantis!
From that day on,
I drooled every time I see him.
Can't believe I would drool over you now...
What a great love story,
though I am a player,
I could never steal someone else's love,
I think you should go back to your Mantis.
Too late, my brother,
fearing Mantis would eat me,
killed him already
No way
That's why I would eat other monsters,
in Mantis's memory and
to piss my brother off!
It does not matter that Mantis died
moonlight box was taken by your brother,
go get it from him
then you can change history.
I get along with my brother just fine
he has never been happier.
If I do change history and return to Mantis
I'm afraid I would miss seeing Zixia,
then I would ruin his love affair!
So there is no way I would want
that moonlight box!
Oh yah?
Haha, such a nice girl
Lucky me,
Come along.
Brother, what can I do to make Zixia Smile
Come...
Easy... Play a game with her
How?
Give me the moonlight box
Here
This game is call time
reversal riskless game
How?
You...
Come here.
Plant a flower in this pile of bullshit,
and throw it at your boss
No way?
Then forget about making her happy
Wait... You, throw this pile of bullshit
at me immediately
Huh?
Ready?
Ready
- Here it comes
- Go ahead
Seriously
Yes
Throw!
Ah! I'm not afraid of you
(Casting spell)
Alright
Isn't it fun?
So close!
Bullshit! Here it comes again
Brother, here it comes
Here you go!
- (Casting spell)
- Faster, faster
It's alright, time has reversed
Brother, will this pile of
bullshit fly around all night?
Not to worry
I am very experienced at
using this moonlight box
I know all of its attributes
Only making the bullshit disappear,
everything will stay in the same form!
Good for you!
Alright
Ah! Bullshit!
Haha...
It's alright, I go wash my face
Haha... what else is fun?
Your sister wants to play,
wait a moment, (Casting spell)!
Where did she go? Hahaha
would you like to know? (Casting spell)
My love for you is destined,
you decide whether to leave with me
Ok, Let's go!
(Casting Spell)!
Told you, he would not leave us behind
Yes, (Casting spell)!
What are you doing?
He is seducing your wife,
trying to use your
moonlight box to run off.
(Casting spell)!
Escape with the moonlight box,
I will hold them back
Stop
God is just like this
Sister you must leave, hurry
Follow me
Cannot leave my brother
(Casting spell)
(Casting spell) (Casting spell)
I will kill this monkey
Do not harm him!!
You saggy old lady, what do you care
if I hit this monkey
Then you wouldn't care if I hit your woman?
She's my woman, of course
it would be my business.
He is not your man...
wait..he's your man
You get to play around, why shouldn't I?
You bitch,
Look what you have done
Who are you calling bitch
Yes I called you bitch, get out of my way
Stop fighting all of you
You shut up
Why are you all fighting over a man
You can for a woman, why can't I?
Shut up,
Who is he?
He is your father's brother
My business again?
Ah, let me down
You damn monkey, I shall forget about
you seducing my wife
but from this day on,
you should treat my ex-wife well!
You marry her tomorrow,
and I will marry Zixia.
Six Ears Monkey, your death is worth it.
Because of you, the Sealed book
will stay true.
Because of you, I stay perfect
as the Heaven of Emperor
nobody would know about
my mistakes in the Sealed Book
The secret dies with you.
I get it..haha
Once Zixia dies, Joker will turn into
the Monkey King and go on the pilgrimage.
What happened? What is this?
Six, someone rewrote the history,
what's matter?
Jade Emperor,
You haven't been to the court for days,
Everyone worries about you
I have the flu,
Need a 21 days quarantine,
in order to prevent it
from spreading to everyone
That's not right.
Sealed book said gods cannot be sick.
But then again,
My deified god has been coughing for days,
Maybe the Sealed book made a mistake.
Mistakes in Sealed Book?
How could it be?
You did not know how to write
the word correctly that day,
mis-spell your own dog's name,
Of course he is coughing now
You uneducated person.
Why don't you go back and reflect on that?
Then how do you explain about
gods getting sick?
Calling me uneducated!
Six, you have to do me another favor,
I promise not to lie to you again.
You lied in the Sealed book,
You lied about your promise to me
I will never trust you again!
Alright, Six, just this one more favor.
I'd rather die!
Then off you go...
When you violated the holy law,
I have already announced
your death sentence
I asked Guanyin to capture you,
put you in the Great Oven to burn
Now it is the third time.
In the holy law, no one can be
sentenced to death three times.
I owe you two times, now you may go!
After you left,
nobody will take Joker's place
as the Monkey King
Protecting the Longevity Monk
in the pilgrimage.
Mankind will be haunted by evil,
The world will collapse, your son will die.
Are you sure about leaving?
What did you just say?
Nothing!
I said nothing, you heard wrong
Didn't you say that I have a son?
You heard wrong, there is no such thing
You are not going anywhere
until you explain everything!
You owe me twice. Say!
Do I have a son or not?
I promised that woman that I won't tell
Say it!
Okok, let me tell you.
Do you remember back then
When I sent you to protect the twin sisters
within Buddha's temple lamp?
What did I do wrong;
Do I have to be born in
the same image as you?
Like I have a choice in this!
You... that girl...
twin sisters?
You must be Qingxia Immortal.
I am Six Ears Monkey,
We are going to spend a lot of
times together, let's be friends!
You? Don't even dream about it.
Is there a problem?
You got hair all over you,
like a rambutant,
Go shave first
Then come back hitting on me again!
Because of what she said,
you shifted into human form
and give yourself a human name.
I took your advice and shaved,
named myself Charlie Chin
You married Qingxia that day,
violated the holy law
just when everyone is
about to execute you, I realized,
you could be the substitute for the
real Monkey King from 500 years later.
Get in the Great Oven.
So I made a deal and released you,
but it is after you have left I realized
Qingxia was pregnant with your child.
Always a knock on the door
when I reach the story climax.
What again
Jade Emperor, please save my sister
What happen to her?
We made peace with each other
but now she is taken by the King Bull
The Sealed Book was written like this,
what can I do about it?
You can...
my husband, my son, my whole family
are making up for your mistake,
I already knew about
the error in the Sealed Book,
I just never told anyone!
What?
When you sent him to the
human world that day,
I overheard everything,
he left without saying goodbye
Because he never wanted to be with me,
so I beg you to return my body to me,
as long as you save Zixia,
I shall end my life,
I promise no one would
learn about this secret
Please, Jade Emperor.
Your body is in the Misty Palace!
Thank you, Jade Emperor!
Why didn't she tell me
that she was pregnant
I asked her the same question!
It is a woman's failure for
not being able to keep her man!
If I kept him tied up using the baby,
He would only stay because of him, not me.
I'd rather let him loose
than making both of us unhappy,
it is my way of loving him.
I took away her body,
and making her sharing one body with Zixia,
sending both of them to the human world
to hone their skills.
As for Qingxia's child,
I also sent him to the human world
using Lady Spring's body,
making Second Chief to take the fall.
Using the moonlight box,
I was able to send him to 500 years ago.
One day in heaven equals 10 years on earth.
Now he is a grown man,
but with the holy spirit in him,
anyone on earth can obtain immortality
by eating his flesh.
I always thought that
I was a bird without legs,
but in fact I have been
a kite without a string.
The so called freedom, has made me
turning away from the ones I love.
I don't wish to miss my second chance.
I shall accompany my son on the pilgrimage.
When I return, I promise to
never leave you again.
This time I will not ask about
your mother's maiden name,
nor would I talk about
the nature of man and demons,
We talked for so long,
would you at least give me a response,
It's basic politeness, get it?
You finally have a response to me
Bully, you sent a deaf-mute to me!
The wedding shall begin...
Hahaha...
Seven color auspicious cloud?
Do not worry, its dry thunder,
not going to rain, see?
Impossible
Who are you?
It's me! Brother
Is it really you?
Lady Bull,
I am a changed man,
Trying to keep a low profile these days,
please behave!
If you are truly my brother,
Why wouldn't you turn around and face me?
I made many mistakes, so I cannot face you.
I had an affair with your wife,
then with other women too,
and then I made someone
else took the fall for me.
I have betrayed all of you!
Yes! Told you I'm not the Monkey King!!
How could it be, I have seen the end.
Joker is the Monkey King,
What happened?
I have done so much wrong.
Now I return, just want a chance
to redeem myself!
Monkey, you have returned!
Master, I have committed great crimes.
Fortunately Guanyin was
able to show me the way
Now I just want to forget about
all the unholy desires of this world,
I shall accompany you on the pilgrimage.
Lord have mercy, you have repented!
You stupid monkey,
calling me sweetheart back then.
Now you call me Miss Bull?
Sweetheart my ass,
you treacherous monkey.
How dare you to ask for my forgiveness
Brother! I use to leave everyone behind,
but now aren't you also preparing to leave
your family, and rob someone else's wife!
And you, stealing other's husband,
and you, believing your love
with Mantis was so pure,
and yet you have murdered so many.
Now you are accomplice
to your brother's crime.
It is not you who are forgiving me today,
It is I who shall spare all of you.
Stupid monkey, today is my brother's
wedding day,
and you dare to interrupt?
Stupid monkey, full of lies!
How dare you to insult me like this!
What are you doing?
I was a thief, breaking locks come easy.
Let's go save the Longevity Monk!
Hurry
You dare to hit my father!
Turn!
Save your toys and go back to school.
Leave the real fighting to the adults.
You damn monkey, we are finished!
Magic Cudgel
Let me finish eating this sweet potato,
I need more carbs.
Ah...
Damn monkey! You dare to
hurt my wife and kid!
I will kill you!
Bring it on
Where you can go
Monster...
take the Longevity Monk with you...
Ok
Zixia! Let go, you baldy!
Sister?
Sorry, I'm late!
Ah! You are the one with
gynecological disease
Brother
Hurry, or we won't have time to finish
this task pre-written in the Sealed Book.
Let's switch clothes and identities.
Brother, are you alright?
Eat me!
What?
Eat me, then your power
till increase greatly
Then you can beat the Monkey King
No!
Xiang Xiang, you are my only sister
Give me the chance to redeem myself,
my life for the death of Mantis
No, no way
Xiang Xiang, I have never
begged you before,
This time I really beg you, okay?
Please, now I beg of you
Ah...
My Gods
Today Monkey King will fight with King Bull
to achieve the goal for
the Buddhist scriptures
Let's go to help him
Yes my lord.
Damn monkey, you have nowhere to run.
This is no problem for me
Damn monkey, called yourself a god
greater than heaven,
well I am even mightier
and I'm going to destroy you!
God soldiers
Let's fight
It's time
Bulls, go to hell
Damn you
Zixia
Don't come closer
Monkey, I cannot have Zixia, so do you.
All surround
Sister
Capture!
Here I come
I am just like my sister,
the one I love,
is a hero who step on
the seven color clouds,
you weren't him before,
but now at the end,
you are him
Rest in peace, you will be revived.
I have made a deal with
the Heaven of Emperor
Capture!
May the Buddha preserve us
Zixia is now dead;
Monkey King shall continue on the
pilgrimage for the Buddhist scriptures
with the Longevity Monk,
The story now comes to a perfect closure.
Brother, Master is telling
you to stop fighting,
- ok off I go. Ah.
- Slow down, Master.
Wait for me.
Brother, I beg of you!
Please... ok off I go.
Hurry up! We are not even close
to reach 1000 miles a day,
Might as well forget about
getting the Buddhist scripture.
What's the rush, Where is he going?
Master, you haven't gotten off the horse
in three days, are you alright?
My ass hurts like hell!
Cut the bullshit! Hurry...
Are you giving me attitude...
Master, wait for me
I will kick your ass if
you fall behind again
Brother, give me a break
He is in such a hurry because
he wants to be reunited with his family!
Why are you stalking me?
You promise to go on separate ways
You are so annoying!
Where you go, I go!
One day in heaven equals 10 years on earth.
Now that the Longevity Monk has obtained
the Buddhist scripture to save mankind.
The gods no longer get ill,
even the deified god has recovered.
The oceans are full of products,
no more lovers committing suicides.
The people are now enjoying healthy
and joyful lives,
death toll deceased significantly.
The underworld gods are very pleased.
The Longevity Monk restored
his rightful identity as the Jinchan son,
and now owns the title
of Zhantan Benefaction Buddha.
Husband, thanks to the mercy
of the Heaven of Emperor,
You may now take my sister's place next me
as the temple lamp wick.
Don't be naive,
My guess is that he wants to keep
a tight watch on our family,
So on one would learn his mistake
in the Sealed Book!
Don't be so judgmental
Damn it! Another mistake
in the Sealed Book,
What do I do? What do I do?